allnutri.com 2009-05-01

# Allnutri.com - Privacy Policy of AllNutri's User Agreement

AllNutri believes that trust is an important component of the service we provide to our customers. To ensure that we earn and keep that trust, AllNutri makes every effort to protect your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you about AllNutri's collection, use and disclosure of information you choose to share with us through the Sites. 

This Privacy Policy is considered to be a part of AllNutri's User Agreement. By using the Sites you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. By using the Sites, you are also consenting to AllNutri's privacy practices, including the use and disclosure of any personally identifiable information that you have shared with us, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**What Information We Collect  
**Information You Give Us. The use of certain features and services on the Sites requires that you register and supply personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, telephone number and other information, which is stored by AllNutri. When you register as a member of the Sites, we may also collect additional information from you in order to provide you with those specific services and to personalize your experience on the Sites. For example, AllNutri.com users may provide more information using. 

Information Gathered Automatically. The Sites use "cookies" to automatically recognize returning users. Cookies used by the Sites may contain your user name, email address, IP address or zip code. A cookie is a small file on your hard drive that allows us to display your previously defined search criteria and notification preferences whenever you visit our site. "Clear gifs" are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and may be used to track the online movements of Web users or to let us know if you have opened an email that we sent you. 

Your access provider assigns an internet protocol address to your computer when you use the Internet. We collect each IP address that accesses the Sites; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; your behavior on the Sites and related services, including the products and merchants you view or searched for, as well as the URL you come from and go to next; cookie number; participating merchants you visit and the items that you purchase. We use this data, as well as other data in our databases, to analyze site and user behavior, troubleshoot technical problems, resolve disputes, address complaints, prepare aggregated reports that we share with others and customize your experience on the Sites. 

You can block cookies by changing the settings on your browser (contact your ISP for help), but doing so may prevent us from delivering certain services to you (e.g., saved searches). Your browser must also be set to accept cookies in order to access the Sites as a registered member. 

**Use of Information by AllNutri  
**Information you provide to us through the Sites is used by AllNutri to operate the Sites, provide you with information and services you request, and to communicate with you. We may, for example, send emails to you including newsletters and alerts. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary . You may always choose not to provide us with this information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time. 

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information  
**Aggregated Research Data. AllNutri produces research reports and other information and data about online shopping for participating merchants, and other customers, as well as media and other interested parties. Such information and data are based on aggregated, anonymous information about millions on online shoppers and do not include any personally identifiable information about individuals. 

Co-Branded Services. AllNutri usually saves information that it collects from users and shares this information with certain partners in order to provide services to users. In order to use certain services on the Sites, it may be necessary for you to enter information that then goes to our partner. The areas of the Sites in which partners are collecting information may be co-branded with our partners' logos. In these cases, the partner's use of user data is governed by their privacy policies, not ours. AllNutri may receive a copy of such information from these partners, subject to the privacy policies of such partners. If you have questions regarding the privacy policy or data collection practices of one of our business partners, please contact that partner directly. AllNutri does not have control over and is not responsible for the data collection and use practices of our business partners. 

Special Offers. On the Sites, you may also have opportunities to express interest in or register for third party products and services. If you do, we will provide data about you to the third party to implement your request. For example, in the AllNutri Cash-Back Program (a service of the Smart Shopper Club) we work with Ebates.com and they may collect information on you such as your name, address, email address or telephone number. For more about Ebates.com's practices and your options regarding their data collection and use, see Ebates.com's Privacy Policy. 

Advertisers. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Sites. These companies may use information about your visits to the Sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. When we do this, we do not provide your name, address, email address or telephone number. 

We may disclose information when required by law or under the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to conform to applicable law, comply with legal process served on AllNutri, or to protect the property or interests of AllNutri, its agents and employees, personal safety, or the public. Under such circumstances, AllNutri may be prohibited by law, court order or other legal process from providing notice of the disclosure, and AllNutri reserves the right not to provide such notice in its sole discretion. 

**Other Use and Disclosure of Information for the Sites  
**Content and Ratings. You can publish reviews, comments and other content. Members can choose to rate products or reviews, and to create a web of trust. As an unregistered visitor, we may allow you to rate products and/or reviews. 

We, and our licensees, can republish your content as described in our User Agreement. We publish product ratings and use them to develop aggregate ratings, personalize site views and merchandise products. We use your review ratings and web of trust to personalize site views and identify/feature popular members. For example, we may promote most popular or highest-earning reviews and members. While we don't expect to transfer the complete review rating and web of trust database to others (except as contemplated elsewhere in this Policy), we use the database throughout our network and to generate results for others. 

Email Tools. If you send emails through our site, your email will include your email address and any personal message you include. Although we do not retain, in any easily-retrievable way, the addresses that you are emailing, these emails are not private communications. Also, you may not use these tools to send spam or content that violates the User Agreement. 

**Links to Other Sites  
**The Sites contain links to other web sites. AllNutri is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. If you have concerns about how other web sites collect and use information about you, make sure to read that site's own privacy policy. 

**Changing or Deleting Information About You  
**Registered members may update or edit personal information or delete their membership account by accessing their Member Profile or Account information. We try to implement changes to our databases as quickly as possible. However, not all databases may be updated immediately, and some old data may remain in our archives and records. Also, we may be unable to send changes you make to partners, vendors or third party service providers who have already received your data or content. If your account or membership is being terminated or suspended, we may maintain some data to prevent re-registration. 

**Security  
**AllNutri uses physical, electronic and administrative safeguards, including advanced firewall and password protection for our databases, designed to protect the security of data. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees that need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.
